BRETT RUSSELL

PROFILE

I am a well-rounded and hardworking employee, currently working in the gaming and hospitality sector.

Through working in this i, I have developed valuable customer service and communication skills.

I have a strong work ethic and always maintain a high level of personal and professional integrity. I enjoy a challenge and am very interested in learning new skills as well as continuing to develop my existing ones.

Alongside my extensive experience in customer service, I also have a keen interest in continuing to work with people and in customer-relations.

CONTACT

Phone:

0422861355

Email:

brett.russell2016@gmail.com

Address:

2601/105 Clarendon Street, Southbank, VIC, 3006

EXPERIENCE

CROUPIER AT CROWN MELBOURNE

APRIL 2018 - PRESENT

- Dealing games including Poker and Blackjack while adhering to VCGLR procedures and protocols.
- Providing customer service and tourism advice for both local and international patrons.
- Being vigilant and consistent in controlling games and managing conflict resolution.
- Quickly and analytically calculating payouts and managing large sums of money.

TOURNAMENT DIRECTOR AT AUSTRALIAN POKER LEAGUE

NOVEMBER 2016 - APRIL 2018

- Overseeing tournaments of up to 80 players.
- Providing excellent customer service and recruiting new players.
- Problem solving and resolving any conflicts between players.
- Providing rulings and distributing payments.

TEAM MEMBER AT KFC WARRAGUL

MAY 2012 - JULY 2016

- Providing customer service and preparing products correctly.
- Serving customers, handling payments, and dealing with complaints and queries.
- Training new staff and teaching procedures and protocols.

EDUCATION

WARRAGUL REGIONAL COLLEGE

Completed Year 12 VCE in 2014.

CHISHOLM INSTITUTE BERWICK

Completed Certificate IV in Accounting in 2017.

SKILLS AND OTHER QUALIFICATIONS

- Certificate III in Hospitality including components in conflict resolution, cultural awareness, and coaching others.
- Proficiency in Microsoft Office products